

PROFILE

Aerospace Engineer with over a year of design and manufacturing process experience in aeronautical field. Highly dedicated and self-motivated with work in responsibility. A fast learner with a passion to learn something new.

Birth date: 4 April 1999

Age: 23

Nationality: Thai Marital Status: Single Driver license: Yes

CONTACT

PHONE:

+66 88-526-2813

EMAIL:

nontapat.ntkn@gmail.com

SKILLS

Communication Skill

- Thai (Native Language)
- English (Intermediate) (Toeic score: 905)

Computational Skill

- SolidWorks (Intermediate)
- Abaqus CAE (Intermediate)
- Ansys Fluent (Intermediate)
- Simcenter 3D (Beginner)
- CATIA (Beginner)
- MATLAB (Beginner)
- Edgecam (Beginner)
- ASC CPC (Intermediate)

NONTAPAT NONTAKANAN

Aerospace Engineer

EDUCATION

Kasetsart University

Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology University Melbourne, Australia | 2019 – 2020 BA Aerospace Engineering (Honours)

Graduated with a GPA of 3.3

Bangkok, Thailand | 2016 - 2019 BA Aerospace Engineering (IDDP Program) Graduated with a GPA of 3.16

Kasetsart University Laboratory School Chonburi, Thailand | 2010 – 2015 Majored in Science-Math

WORK EXPERIENCE

Thai Airways [Internship]

2019 - 2020

- Designed the specific drone regarding aircraft inspection purpose in conceptual approach
- Participated in inspection process of the engine

RV Connex - Aircraft Design Engineer

March 2021 - Present

- Designed and analysed structure of the Unmanned-Aerial Vehicle via the Finite Element Method and Computational Fluid Dynamics Approaches including verification test
- Experienced manufacturing processes of composite-based part which are prepreg autoclave, infusion, hand lay-up and CNC machine
- Participated R&D program of prepreg autoclave approach to enhance better characteristic and structure of further UAV

CERTIFICATES

SolidWorks - Advanced Part Modeling (2021)

Deti Training Center - Authorised SolidWorks Training

SolidWorks - Surface Modeling (2021)

Deti Training Center - Authorised SolidWorks Training

Autoclave Operation Training (2022)

ASC Training